I don't want nobody to get killed
I come and get you, I'm always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame where all is spread
Oh, I don't take all of the blame, you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
No sun, no light, such a mess, I love them
Don't kill your heart, you make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, the changes to power
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my top, the shadows of the earth
Illusions are born
The golden end is still wrong, but I know it's a pain
That makes us a human after all
Toin to save you for the control
About your precious worth
This scar may respond to your call
Today, we've gathered all nobles with the progenitors' blood to address a growing concern
Humans!
The Japanese Imperial Demon Army has been wrapping up operations and increasing their numbers in northern Tokyo
This human organization is killing our brothers
Human organization?
Explaining their territory and flirting with forbidden enchantments to increase their power
According to our intel, they are once again experimenting on the Seraph of the End
If we allow these humans to continue to rise and gain strength
Another plague like the one that occurred eight years ago will surely come to pass
You needn't worry about that
Because we're exterminating the Japanese Imperial Demon Army
We're going to war
To ensure that we continue to rule this world
We'll have to slaughter the greedy livestock resistance once and for all
Extermination
The Seraph of the End
Don't worry you
I'm coming to your rescue soon
That's all I have to report from block three, sir
I'm Imperial Demon Army Major General Shinya Hiragi
I'll be covering reports from the Kansai region
Several of them concern suspicious vampire activity
Among other things
Ichinose
Hey, quit sawing logs
Huh?
Are we finally done with this boring-ass meeting?
Drop the attitude, Gurren
You're not as special as you might think
Sorry, General
It's just so hard to remember that
When I'm surrounded by the dullest personalities in the army
Is that so?
Well, I can beat the lesson into you
Pardon me, sir
Ichinose's attitude is nothing new to this room
Now, as I was saying
I'm taking it off
You can send me all of the information later
Come on, Gurren
I can't defend you forever
You're gonna have to adjust your attitude sooner or later
Huh?
I never ask you to defend me
You Hiragis control the Imperial Demon Army
You don't need a second-class Ichinose hanging around
So, I'm out
I've got some sleep to catch up on
At least you know your place, deadweight
We'll handle things like we always have
Without you
It's a wonder humanity's still kicking
Later
Feels like I lost a few brain cells
You can't hide from me today, Gurren!
There's no beating around the bush with you
It's kind of refreshing after dealing with pointless politics all day
You know what I'm after
Now quit wasting my time and give me a cursed gear
I can handle the demon
Oh, yeah?
Does this have anything to do with getting vengeance for your family?
Of course
It's the only thing I've lived for ever since you brought me here
We need to get you a date
Soon
I better pacify this idiot before he makes a scene
Last thing I need is him getting the Hiragi's attention
Fine
Let's go make a contract with the demon
Then, you'll join us on the front line
Huh?
No joke?
Sure, why not?
I don't care if you haven't finished your training
That way it's your fault if you die
Like we need to worry about that happening
I'm a badass
I'll be slaying monsters from dusk till dawn
You really are an idiot, huh?
Oh, and there's one more thing, you
Huh?
That's for trying to kick a superior officer
The burdens of command can really take it out of you
But I've got to admit
Things are getting a lot less boring around here
What happened to your head?
Let me guess, you skipped class and got into another fight?
What's it to you?
You should know, Gurren doesn't pull any punches by now
Um, why'd you ask if you knew?
It's fun
Congrats, by the way
On the demon contract
He finally approved it, didn't he?
Yeah, but you know him
He makes a choice on a whim and doesn't follow through
You can't fool me
I can tell you're nearly bursting at the seams
No, I'm not
Don't worry about it
Lieutenant Colonel Gurren may have a razor-sharp tongue
And a general fondness for brutality
But he always keeps his promises
Finally
It's happening
I'll get the power to kill those parasites
The time is near
You must be overjoyed
It won't be long until you get the chance to see your precious angel again
I have such high hopes for you, Mika
You're certainly fellow
I have such high hopes for our own
Thank god
Come on, hurry!
It's all right.
Alright, pay attention.
I've already finished grading your written exams, so I'll just be handing those out and
calling it a day, okay?
Remember, this score is crucial to your overall Cursed Gear ranking.
The way you perform in class is just as important as in training.
I expect those of you with less than passing grades to put extra effort into your studies
from now on.
Let me see!
Give it back!
Oh, wow!
Would you look at the score?
How impressive!
Hey, cut it out!
You've really outdone yourself.
They say only superhumans can get a score like this!
What being such a pest?
Don't you want to share it?
You should be so proud!
Give that back to me!
How'd he get zero points?
That takes a special kind of dumb.
Whoa, that's crazy!
I thought my handwriting sucked, but this guy takes the pain.
What's your problem?
Can't you find someone else to annoy?
Now is that any way to talk to a lady?
Especially one who's trying to help you fit in.
You could try to show some gratitude.
You can take your gratitude and choke on it!
I'll tell you what I keep telling Gurren.
I don't need friends to stick it to the bloodsuckers.
Are we clear?
Yeah, we're as clear as crystal.
Just don't come crying to me when you realize that you're completely worthless by yourself.
Oh, yeah?
I'll kill 50 of those fangs with my eyes closed.
Said the childish fool.
You're a childish fool!
Come on, it makes sense that you failed.
Huh?
Sorry, that didn't come out like I meant it to.
I'm just saying that since you spent several years as a prisoner of the vampires,
your Japanese reading and writing skills aren't as strong as your English and Latin are.
So, it makes sense that you failed.
Uh, well, yeah, that goes without saying.
That excuse is crappier than your test score, huh?
How would you know?
Then what's your score?
It better be epic or I'll pop you in for being an arrogant ass.
Come on, Four Eyes, let's see how smart you really are.
See for yourself.
Latin, English, and Japanese spellcraft.
Easy stuff.
Foreign languages aren't even my strong suit.
I should be no match for a seasoned study abroad poser like you.
How about I use you for vamp-killing practice?
Yeah, tough guy.
Come on, let's see you try.
You, please stop fighting.
Waiter, are you too scared to throw a crotch?
By the way, I still haven't dismissed you from class yet.
Go ahead, open your stupid mouth one more time.
I can do the world a favor and end you right here.
Hey, I can hear you morons halfway down the hall.
What's the deal?
Welcome back, Lieutenant Colonel Gurren.
I hope everything went well.
As well as you'd expect.
What else is new?
Anyway, is there a reason for all the racket?
Those two.
I should have known.
Wait, let's put this on hold for now.
Gurren's come out of hiding.
What's the deal?
I thought you said I was gonna get to contract with a demon.
How much longer do I have to wait-
Let me do the talking.
Way too loud.
With all due respect, I think you owe us an explanation.
You have an obligation to this class,
but you left for over ten days without any regard for your students.
I think giving us some cursed gear would make up for that.
Really?
You think a bunch of dumbass losers like you have what it takes to tangle with a demon, huh?
No doubt about it.
The only dumbass in here is Kimizuki.
I won't fail.
Your test score says otherwise.
I won't ask for your opinion.
So, what's your assessment?
Can this class resist the demon's temptation?
Hmm.
Well, there's always room for improvement.
But those two are much stronger than I was at 16.
I think they could do it.
What about the others?
There are a few contenders.
But Yoichi Saotume takes the cake.
He has a surprisingly high stability against demons.
Really?
Okay then.
Why don't we give it a shot now?
It's less complicated that way.
No!
You can't do that in the classroom!
Oh my!
Are you planning to attack?
This sure got interesting fast.
Hope you're ready, kids.
If you die from this, blame yourselves for not training hard enough.
No!
Dude!
What the hell is going on?
It feels just like...
My heart's been squeezed.
What's wrong with everyone?
I think that's enough for now.
Alright, good.
If you're still conscious, you've got a chance.
Make no mistake.
You've got a long way to go.
But if you continue to train and study your spellcraft,
you could move into the contract ceremony for a cursed gear.
The five of you that are still on your feet?
You just turned yourself four stars.
You'll get to try out for a black demon series cursed gear.
The same rank of weapon as my sword.
Well...
I guess there's only three.
You.
Kimizuki.
And Yoichi.
I wish you had passed out.
Dealing with demons is like a day at the beach for you, isn't it?
Guess I should expect as much from General Haragi's daughter.
You probably didn't even use a ward.
What a turn-off.
Oh, don't be that way.
You know I'm the cutest thing you've ever seen in your life.
Piss off.
Let's go before I change my mind.
So, uh, Lieutenant Colonel Gurren, I know I should expect unconventional tests and tactics from you,
but I'm not entirely sure letting Yoichi try out for the black demon series is a good idea.
Do you have a problem with my decision?
No, sir, that's not what I'm saying.
It's just, I'm not certain he has enough strength to accept a demon into...
Tough.
If he doesn't have the strength, he dies.
That's the world we live in.
We're not playing games here.
But, sir...
For crying out loud.
Yoichi, tell me.
You still want to avenge your sister's death at the hands of the vampires, don't you?
Yes, of course.
All right.
Are you willing to die for it?
I don't know.
Then you should quit right now.
If you have any doubts, go back up those stairs.
Go, Yoichi.
This isn't the kind of place a nice guy like you should be, and you know it.
No matter how hard I cover my ears, I still hear it.
I'm still under the bed, frightened.
Did you not hear what I said?
Get out of here.
I've made up my mind.
I'm doing it.
This is the only way I'll get the strength I need.
I have to make sure that nothing in this world can take away the people I hold dear ever again.
Damn.
In the end, he's no different than I am.
Hmm.
All right.
Let's keep moving, people.
Time for the ceremony.
right?
All right.
Yeah.
Come on.
Isn't that old?
I'm gonna pick this up.
Hmm, I'm hungry, right?
Just a clear step.
I say welcome.
I'll stay the same.
All right, let's keep moving people time for the ceremony
Hey, getting cold feet now isn't gonna help
There's no point worrying about it
Deal with it, you've made your choice
Are you sure you'll be able to deal with it, Kamizuki?
You were standing at first, then you leaned over
Was the demon too much to handle?
You saw it too, right, Yoichi?
Me? Well, yeah
Stop paying attention to the small things
They weren't the only ones who saw it, Kamizuki
In fact, I remember you being in a lot of agony
The last thing you should be doing is getting too comfortable, you
The demon you'll make a contract with is much stronger than the last one
If you let your guard down for an instant, it'll kill you
Yeah, I already know
Welcome to the edge of hell
Where is this a temple?
It's the home of the thing you want most of all
The highest ranking weapons with demon kings sealed inside them are kept here
The highest ranking, huh?
So, if I have one of these, I can kill the vampires?
That depends on your personal skill
Okay, but they're all the same as your sword, right?
Yes
The rare black demon series
Quit asking questions
Let's get started
I've got more important things to do than hang out in a dark cellar with a group of newbies
Fine
What do I have to do?
Pick a weapon you like and enter the spell circle
Once you touch the weapon, the contract ceremony will begin automatically
If you don't lose to the demon, you'll gain its power
And what if we do, Lix?
You'll either become a man-eating monster, or the demon's power will crush your soul and kill you
Either way, you'll end up dead
If you start to go monster on us, I'll kill you myself
Fine by me
I've been waiting a long time for a chance like this
Besides, I'd rather fight with the demon than sit through another boring lecture
The vampires will suffer
For Mika and my family, I'll exterminate every last one of them
That's the only thing I still live for
Then draw, and it'll begin
All right, you bastard, let's dance
Give me your power
I'llister, let's dance
作詞・作曲・編曲 初音ミク
作詞・編曲 初音ミク
編曲 初音ミク
Thank you.